Poor them.
This beef piece looks delicious!
It may look like beef shank, but it's not.
It's the beef skirt.
At first, I kinda avoid the beef flank because it may contain fat.
But this one has lots of tendons.
But first, let me stir this up...
This is the dipping sauce that I prepare.
I always need fish sauce.
You eat Vietnamese food, you add
the fish sauce for a better aroma, always.
Color Man Fish sauce?
Hey, you should use our Color Man Fish Sauce,
Hoang Anh, tell your boyfriend to buy from us.
Can we talk in private later?
I wanna propose our products.
Just one look and I know for sure.
Now, just add a little bit of fish sauce.
Sliced chili pepper.
Legendary dipping sauce.
Y'all wanna try this?
Beef skirt, everyone.
First time hearing this.
Nga is focusing on eating alone, she doesn't care about anything.
Ain't even enjoying the dish.
No wonder you're an F.A.
This beef piece is so tender and sweet.
So sweet.
Make sure it's fully covered with the sauce.
So great! And now let me
show you what the special bowl has.
First one should be the Rare beef.
Beef flank, with fat.
Some people really enjoy the fat of beef.
I prefer the lean beef flank.
Yeah, I prefer this one, the beef skirt.
A whole ox can be butchered
into various parts, various types of meats.
An ox is heavy,
but its meat isn't as heavy.
- No wonder it's so expensive.
- And beef meatballs.
Five-way special Pho bowl, right?
What's the last one?
I believe it would be the beef tendon.
I see, and where is that piece?
- I think it must be this one.
- No, it's not.
Here, let me show you. This one is the beef tendon.
I don't have any tendon pieces. Perhaps I am full of tension.
Finally, I found it!
I love beef tendons.
Five-way special Pho Bowl!
Awesome!
It's quite chewy.
I also love beef tendons.
But this is a bit too much...
If you are on a diet, you should order fewer noodles.
Rare beef.
Can I have some more Hoisin sauce? It's so good.
I really enjoy the Hoisin sauce.
Shit, I forgot to season my bowl the entire time.
It's so good. I forgot to season it.
Now the Sirachai sauce...
Wow, this is the first time Nga says she's full.
This Pho Bowl is too big for us.
I forgot everything.
It's delicious enough to make me forget everything!
Can I have some vegetables?
Herbs and Sawleaf.
The noodles are quite pliable.
Pliable and aromatic.
Careful, don't stick your finger into my bowl.