I need to dip it with this.
And don't forget about the sauce...
This is already my second bowl.
- It's good, right?
- Yes.
Continue.
Do Mrs. Van and the kids eat this?
I'll buy for them too.
Order a couple of portions to take home.
Get me five portions.
Five takeaway portions, please.
Cool.
I'll take care of it.
Let me catch my breath.
It's delicious, Mr. Thong.
Mr. Pham Minh Thong.
Let me try this.
Only 18,000 VND for this?
Remember to check-in on Facebook.
You'll get a free drink.
Use the code "Hoang Anh".
You will get a free drink.
She's bluffing.
You'll be in trouble if people don't get any free stuff.
Use the code "Hoang Anh"
and take a picture, you'll get a free drink.
I'm sure you're that boy's girlfriend.
Nonsense.
Or that boy is having a crush on you.
I find it's strange that she's here.
There's must be a reason.
One thing for sure,
it's delicious!
There's a reason that will surprise you.
What's that?
I'll tell you later.
Tell him the reason.
What is it?
What's the reason?
It was Nga's idea.
I don't know anything.
I just did what she told me to.
- What's the reason?
- We miss you.
We haven't met you for a while.
Since we're all here...
Why would you give me a microphone at this time?
Put the microphone on your shirt
and tell me the real reason.
- We have to face it, right?
- That's right.
- Actually...
- Can I have the receipt?
Can I wait for the receipt?
Tell me before the receipt comes.
Actually, we were planning to have breakfast...
First of all, we missed you.
We wanted to meet you and learn more from you.
Then, when we entered this place...
We have another 5 takeaway portions.
It's only 414,000 VND for three bowls.
- Add the rest to this receipt.
- Yes, five special portions.
They're buying me this meal.
All jokes aside.
I must apologize to the chef.
This bowl is too big for me.
And I finished the bowl from Mr. Manager.
But it's so delicious.
Please, listen to us.
Hurry up.
Actually, we really wanted to meet you.
When we got here and looked at the menu...
But we forgot to bring money with us.
"Turn on the air-conditioner,
I have a customer to meet".
Go on.
None of us brought any money.
We couldn't just walk out.
I'm going to curse here.
I thought she had money with her.
I also thought that she would have money with her.
We already ordered two drinks.
It wouldn't be nice to just walk out like that.
I know that if we call you...
you will save us.
We saw your livestream this morning.
You were near here.
So we called you.
But I don't have any money with me.
I mean it.
- You don't have any money with you?
- Yes.
I saw you in your livestream this morning...
I used it to buy Banh Mi.
Let's come up with something.
I used up all my money.
Does your driver have any money?
How about the cameraman?
- Good idea.
- Where's my receipt?
The cameraman has a lot of money.
His pocket is thick.
His pocket is really thick.
Is there anyone left?
He nods his head.
It's 460,000 VND.
Five takeaway portions are 600,000 VND.
It's 1,014,000 VND.
Pay for us.
We'll return the money tomorrow.
Can I borrow a pen?
You have to make a promise.
In front of the camera and
2.5 million audiences of mine.
Promise.
He helps me pay 1,014,000 VND.
The waiter is named Thin.
At 11 AM.
I will repay the money tomorrow.
1,014,000 VND.
Everyone, you heard her.
Everything will be settled
if there's a video about them paying me back the money.
If not, I'll make them pay.
Joking!
I'll pay.
Seal it with your blood.
That's your promise.
You wanted this.
There it is.
We're saved.
We'll pay you back tomorrow.
You should watch out for these girls.
What are you talking about?
That's how they treat you.
It's dangerous.
I'm innocent.
The broth is good.
It's so delicious
that he has to finish it.
The broth is really delicious.
I ate almost two bowls.
Let's have another meatball.
The flank meat is delicious.
I'll ask for extra flank meats next time.
It's skirt steak.
Stop saying it wrong.
Goodbye, everyone.
You are my witnesses.
I cannot forgive this.
- Pay me back before Tet.
- Yes.
- Don't let it pass Tet.
- We don't do that here.
Or I'll come to your house during Tet.
We'll deal with it before Tet.
We'll pay him back the money.
Introduce a little bit about this place.
This Vien Pho noodles stall.
The address is A65 Nguyen Trai Street,
Nguyen Cu Trinh Ward, District 1.
The number is
028 62 70 40 55
Again.
Vien Pho noodles stall.
A65 Nguyen Trai Street,
Nguyen Cu Trinh Ward, District 1.
The number is
028 62 70 40 55
The owner of this place is a fan of mine,
the "Street Cry" show and the "Lifetime show".
Mr. Pham Minh Thong.
I'm doing this to support him.
Also to let everyone remember about these two.
See you again.
What kind of year is this?!