The dough looks good.
- Is there parchment paper?
- Is it the right one?
- We're looking for parchment paper.
- Is it correct?
Let the dough rest for about 45 minutes to 1 hour.
It looks good already.
We can eat while waiting.
Mrs. Truc sends us lots of nice dishes today.
Have you found the bag yet?
Not yet.
- I'll scrape the bowl.
- I'll hold the bowl for you.
Sure. You two can hold it for me.
I'll scrape it.
Or you wanna try?
- Yes. Let me do it.
- Ok. I'll hold the bowl.
- You're so skillful.
- Not at all. I just go for it.
I don't think it works.
Then you can only hold the bowl, just like me.
Since no one helps, I have to do it then.
Let's scrape the bowl.
It looks nice.
The smell is good too.
Merry Christmas and happy new year, everyone! Let's put it in!
I'm not sure how this dough
can turn into those cookies.
- I'm sure.
- Keep your hopes up.
- Every time we get in the kitchen together to make something...
- Remember the bread?
Yeah right, we messed it all up in that 1-hour video.
It must be annoying to watch that video if you're a baker.
But some audiences said they'd love to
watch those clumsy and natural videos of me.
Alright. Let's cover it.
- It's so cool.
- Well, now, we have to...
- let the dough rest.
- Are we done with this?
Yeah, you can put it in the sink.
- Ok.
- Do we put the dough in the fridge?
Yes.
How many hours does it need to rest?
About 45 minutes.
Ok, see you again after 45 minutes.
We're gonna make... Oops, sorry, hon!
We'll be back and do it better.
It's mealtime!
Guys, let's eat with us!
We have a big pot of broth.
- You wanna eat that?
- Yeah.
It's Tuna Rice Noodles.
- You guys wanna have Tuna Rice Noodles or these dishes?
- Gee, there's sweet soup too.
We're gonna eat these.
It's like beef steak wrapped in pastry.
Wow, what a good chef Truc is!
It looks amazing.
True that.
There's bacon too.
It's a dish made by Saigon Gourmet. Superb!
Yep, a nice dish by Saigon Gourmet.
- I forget what kind of beef this is.
- Wagyu?
Beefsteak?
Let me check it again.
Let's dig in! Each gets a piece.
I should try it anyway.
Thank Truc for the meal!
- This salad is from...
- Maestro Kitchen.
Let's eat it right from the container then.
It's Tuna Salad from Maestro Kitchen.
Call 18000 88809!
We'll get back to the cookies after the meal.
- Gosh, this dish looks so nice. You want some, Van Anh?
- This is beef wrapped in...
Yes, please give me a piece.
It's Beef Wellington.
Let me introduce to you this dish - Beef Wellington!
Here it is.
Give Van Anh a piece.
- Do you want a big piece or a small piece?
- A small piece, please.
- Don't worry. You can share with daddy.
- Nah, I'm gonna have Tuna Rice Noodles.
- Why?
- I'm not fond of these dishes.
- This is delicious.
- I agree.
Give me the plate.
- Don't forget the bacon.
- Beef Wellington, guys.
So, these are the products of Saigon Gourmet.
Alright. Here you go.
Daddy, you should try a little.
- Do I need the knife?
- Yes, so you can cut the beef.
Let me show you. You should hold the knife like this.
- It will be easier to cut.
- Where's the ketchup?
It's here.
Here you go.
- Just give me a small piece.
- Ok.
Merry Christmas! Let's try it!
Oh wait, what is this dish?
It's Baked Pork Chop Rib.
OMG! It's huge.
How can we finish them all?
Another fantastic dish.
Absolutely!
It looks like a spare rib, right?
Yeah. It's actually pork chop rib.
The marinade of Maestro is always wonderful.
- They have an exclusive recipe.
- Yeah. Very good.
I'm gonna get some salt and pepper.
Alright. Please enjoy the meal with us.
Wish you all a Merry Christmas
and happy new year!
- Van Anh, do you want some pepper?
- Yes.
Well, this is not a beefsteak review video though.
We planned to film the cookie making process
but here we are eating again.
We'll get back to the cookies soon.
Hello!
It's rolling time!
Now...
Gee, you make it stick to the pin.
Come on, please wait for my instruction.
What's wrong?
Stop it, darling.
Cover the dough before rolling it.
Wait! Some dough's still stuck on the pin.
Darling, put it somewhere else.
Let's divide the dough in half.
Let's divide it.
Yeah, 1 part for me.
How about 3 parts?
2 parts will do.
I'll be the supervisor.
All good.
Be delicate! Yours has got too thin, Thuy Anh.
It's supposed to be even. See?
This area is thicker than the rest.
Roll until it gets even.
The dough should be flat.
Let's check it. Hold on!
Alright.
Take it slow!
Don't press too hard.
The dough is too thin now, Van Anh.
Be delicate!