Hello, everyone!
I have just finished...
live-streaming with Mrs. Lan...
and her shoulder pole serving baguettes
with grilled beef in lolot leaves.
Currently, I'm on Bui Vien street.
I'm looking for a good place
with a reasonable price to rent.
Next year, I plan to open...
an eatery or a coffee shop nearby.
I can see this place is kinda quiet this morning.
I wonder what this place is like in the evening.
I'm having a coffee.
Now I'm gonna...
I think...
I should find an eatery.
I heard there are many eateries on Bui Vien street.
I don't know if there's any hidden gem here.
I want to do a food review.
- Okay.
- Thanks a lot.
Yea.
What is it?
Hoang Anh?
I'm listening!
Hello? You hear me?
What's up?
Where are you now?
Well, I'm having a coffee.
It's because I haven't seen you for a while.
What?
Well, hey...
Don't you have to work at the store today?
- You wanna have breakfast?
- What?
Speak louder. I didn't catch that.
I wonder if you've had your breakfast.
You haven't eaten anything, right?
What?
Have you had your breakfast?
What did you say? I can't hear you.
Hello? Can you hear me?
Speak as loud as possible!
Hello?
I believe everyone here can hear me.
Alright.
I'm having a coffee on Bui Vien street.
Where are you?
Bui Vien street? I'm in district 1, too.
I'm at Vien's pho eatery. It's easy to spot.
What is it called?
Vien's pho eatery.
Its address?
It's at A65 Nguyen Trai street, district 1.
Copy that.
Yeah.
- Is it near the roundabout?
- Yeah.
That's right.
You'll reach the place
after passing the roundabout.
That's alright. I'm gonna check the map later.
Alright.
See you there.
Hold on. Text me the...
What is it called?
- The address.
- You mean the location.
Yeah, that would be better.
- Alright. Let me send it.
- Good. So be it.
Gosh!
Well, I should...
Let's go with me!
What are these two girls up to?
I wonder what Nga Xoai Chua
and Hoang Anh are up to.
Let me see if they find a good eatery or not.
Or they may plan to pull a prank on me.
Okay.
Get the car.
- Yes?
- Can I have the bill?
That guy's already paid it.
Is that so? Alright. I'm good to go now.
- Thank you!
- No, thank you!
- Good luck on your business.
- Thanks a bunch.
She's way too lovely.
Oh dear! I'm here.
It's really easy to spot this place.
There used to be many bars here.
There were a lot of bars & pubs here.
Those places were quite popular back then.
Party people came here quite frequently.
She thought I didn't know
this place or something.
A65.
Vien's pho eatery.
Are you Color Man?
- Pardon?
- Are you Color Man?
Yes, I am.
What brings you here?
Well, they asked me to come here.
You're with these 2 ladies?
Yeah, I'm with them.
Please, take a seat.
Please take a seat, sir.
Shouldn't he sit here?
- Where do you want to seat?
- Anywhere.
Can you scooch over?
Yeah, this seat has the back cushion.
Okay.
I'd love to sit here.
This seat has a nice background.
- I see.
- Alright.
Why are there water on the table?
- Could you wipe it?
- I asked them to.
- Could you please help me?
- Yes.
You were somewhere nearby?
Yes, Bui Vien street.
I was looking for a place to rent.
I was searching for a place.
I thought you wanted to have a coffee there.
Well, I also had a chat with some ladies there.
I see.
If you want to rent a place,
you should ask the locals first.
Ate anything?
- Not yet.
- We waited for you.
- Why?
- Well, it's politeness, you know.
- We waited for you.
- I've already had breakfast.
- Is that true?
- I just want to swing by.
- What?
- But I think you shoud give it a try.
- What did you order?
- We haven't ordered anything.
Vien's pho eatery, huh?
How did you wind up here?
I didn't go out on the Christmas holiday...
so I decided to hang out with her today.
She said as if she's
having many irons in the fire.
Well, I really am.
Please come to my store, Herbal Nature:
1369 Huynh Tan Phat street.
- It's 1389!
- Oops. I mean 1389 Huynh Tan Phat.
Welcome to Herbal Nature.
I didn't go out 'cuz
I was afraid there were traffic jams.
That's why today
I asked her to hang out with me.
You should know that they are still...
working with Color Man.
They haven't quit their job yet.
Many people asked about that.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Many people asked if
you two were still working with me.
- We're still working.
- Tomorrow, Street Cry 4.0 will be filmed.
I'll be there tomorrow.
I'm gonna be the cashier.
- Really?
- Yes. I'm the cashier.
Remember our character has many regulars.
Alright.
1389, keep that in mind.
Shall we order some food now?
Could I have the menu, please?
They serve pho only?
Anything else besides pho?
Besides pho dishes, we also serve...
various types of soup.
- Pho and soup?
- Correct.
We're specialized in beef pho.
- So pho is your main dish?
- Yes.
What would you like to eat?
- I haven't decided yet.
- Gosh! Then take a look!
Why don't you check it first?
After you, sir.
Give me a break.
Well...
- What do you suggest?
- Our top dish is 5-topping special pho.
- I see.
- 5-topping pho?
Yeah, it's a full-topping pho.
What are they?
That serving has rare beef,
meatballs, brisket, tendon.
- Alright.
- We'd like to order that.
3 servings, please.
It's on me.
- Who?
- Me!
They are the bosses now.
They have a billion-dollar startup.
- Yes?
- What do you want to drink?
What's that drink?
It's the herbal drink.
If you check in, you'll get that for free.
Don't order your drink.
Check in first!
I can get a herbal drink?
- I haven't checked in yet.
- I'd like to have that. I'll check in later.
Alright.
Can I have pho for free?
I'm afraid not.
You can just get a drink for free.