Okay.
Just do it gently, okay?
This type of dough is pretty soft.
It isn't the same as the bread dough.
Roll it gently and don't press it.
Don't press it.
This part is flat.
Roll it from the center.
Look.
Easy on it.
You need to roll it evenly.
You see it's bumpy here?
Take it slow.
Don't just focus on 1 spot.
Is it good enough?
It's bumpy!
You know what. It is not...
hard enough.
Van Anh, are you doing well?
I really don't know how to lift this up.
It's too soft.
Let's do it.
Get the cutter, kid.
- Give her a cutter.
- Wait for it. Let me do this first.
Wait for your mom, okay?
Here. You can cut this.
Pick a cutter.
Let me help you.
Last Christmas, we had a trip to Danang.
We visited Hoian.
This year we're trying to make some cookies.
It's economical.
And safe.
Yeah, it's economical and safe.
Can I get the snowman cutter?
- Over there.
- Where?
You lift this up.
Don't just put it there.
You made a mistake.
I don't think we should press this on.
You should just use the cutter.
Don't press it.
It's broken now.
Why is it so soggy?
It really is.
Honey, it's too soggy.
Don't ask me!
What should we do now?
We should just use the cutter only.
- This one only?
- Yeah.
Yeah, that one.
Yay! I made it.
I've made it! I am so cool.
- Wait. I bought those.
- You bought it?
- I bought them in the bookstore.
- You didn't.
- No!
- No, I made them.
- It's not like that.
- I've just baked them.
Nope! They've been here for a while.
We should take a break to
enjoy these cookies now.
Then we can go to bed.
You should have followed my recipe.
She's eating one now.
- We're done here.
- Wait, what?
What a waste!
- It's too soggy.
- I think we can go on.
We can't even lift it.
The dough is too soggy!
I think it needs more flour.
It's too soggy.
Because it has butter.
Maybe we didn't ferment
the dough long enough.
- I think we can make it.
- Not long enough?
- Maybe.
- I don't think so. It took us quite long.
It took an hour?
Just consider that I baked these.
No, you didn't.
You didn't bake them at all.
Fine. Alright!
- It's too soggy!
- Don't say goodbye so early!
We have to stay calm and cure them!
She's gonna be a cookie doctor.
Let me...
Just let her fix it.
What do I do now?
Daddy and I have nothing to do.
Go to bed!
You're being unfair.
Let's go to bed.
No.
Awesome, huh?
You created such a mess then go to bed?
Oh dear.
It's a star, everyone.
We should stop using the cutter.
Use your hands to shape it.
That's faster.
Am I right?
Leave it for me. What are you doing?
I'm gonna make a snowman.
Can I roll it?
Wow! It looks great.
It's better now.
Try this one.
Will it be okay?
- I haven't tried yet.
- Let me see.
It doesn't go so well.
I think this one is much better than that.
Use the spatula to lift it.
I think it's fine enough.
They say failure teaches success.
It's so much better now.
It isn't soggy anymore.
- It wasn't soggy. It was sticky.
- It's better to keep it chilled.
Or we can just keep doing it.
- Just do it.
- Or we can leave it for tomorrow.
No! We must do it now.
We need to do it.
- Let's do it.
- Then help me!
- Don't roll it too flat.
- Yes, mom.
Any wax paper left?
Bring me the max paper.
They're really patient, huh?
They're trying hard.
Truc!
What was that?
Remember not to roll it too flat.
Or else it would get broken.
You listening?
Alright.
It's too flat! I've warned you!
Oh, you did the same!
I've told you that. Don't you listen?
You've ruined it.
It could take forever.
I'm getting mad.
Don't roll it flat, okay?
It could get broken.
Since we didn't keep it chilled,
it will get broken if you roll it flat.
Van Anh's got one.
Give me the spatula.
Let me get it.
It's a mess now.
It's because you rolled it too flat.
That's alright.
Failure teaches success. Go on.
Going on teaches...
Well...
Mommy.
Anything else?
I'm looking for...
Mommy!
You can use this.
Look at your mom.
Lovely Santa!
What is that?
Stop making such a mess!
You've already ruined yours!
Where is the star cutter?
Van Anh?
I don't know.
You used it to make...
What is it called?
Dalgona.
I don't know where it is.
I put it away.
Alright.
You seem nervous.
Yeah, right.
Let's hope for the best.
It's the last hope.
I think it's gonna be alright.
It's good enough.
Hope it will be fine.
Fine. Let's hope!
This Christmas tree looks funny.
- It's broken.
- We're so done.
It's sticky.
♪ We're a happy family ♪
Nah we're an unlucky family.
Yeah.
Eat it.
- Well...
- Put it in the fridge. We'll do this tomorrow.
Guess we'll get back to this tomorrow.
Let's see if we're going to succeed.
- What if...
- Well tomorrow...
This is a pretty long video clip now.
Here are the teasing cookies.
Okay.
Those are for the unlucky bakers!
These are just the teasing cookies.
Yeah. Oh, teasing cookies!
There will be official cookies tomorrow.
The official ones won't be like this.
Hurry up. Say something for
the viewers on this holiday.
Merry Christmas!
What will you say?
- I wish you...
- I wish you guys...
Happiness and bliss.
I wish you all have a joyful Christmas!
A new year is coming! I hope it's gonna
be a year of luck and happiness.
Happy?
See you in the next episode.
Alright.
It's still fine after refrigerating?
Of course it is!
We'll get back to it.
I have a faith that we'll succeed tomorrow.
- It's not gonna be the same.
- Or the day after.
Or one day we will make it.
Or we may succeed next month.
Fossil cookies, perhaps.