You will get free drinks.
Alright, you two want special servings?
- What does it include?
- 5 different types.
- It's a mixed serving.
- Here, five-way special.
- We have three-, and two-way specials as well.
- Wow.
For a two-way special, you will get extra beef.
Oh, you see the price?
- Come on. It's nothing.
- It's all good.
- No problems.
- So luxury.
Don't make me pay later.
- Of course.
- It's our treat.
That's old as the earth.
Five-way specials are 125,000 VND each.
- Yes.
- A piece of cake.
Three-ways are also 120,000 VND.
What does one include?
- Rare beef, brisket, and tendon.
- I see.
Two-ways?
- Either rare beef and tendon, or rare beef and flank. Yes.
- I can choose, right?
- The most important thing is you will get extra beef.
- Correct.
That's out of the question.
I don't eat that much.
- My serving is usually average. Fewer noodles for me.
- Alright.
- I understand.
- I want a five-way special.
- I see. Fewer noodles.
- Yes.
And... A five-way special.
What does it include again?
- Rare beef, brisket, tendon, beef balls, and flank.
- Right.
Brisket, tendon, beef balls, and flank.
Rare beef, brisket, tendon, beef balls, and flank
Alright, I will try that.
- OK. You want drinks?
- Alright.
No, I had some winter melon juice.
- It was 18,000 VND?
- Here.
- So cheap.
- It's good.
It goes with...
- How old is this place?
It was opened on the 28th...
- Last year?
- It's been...
- Around this time last year.
- So it's new.
- Do you know this girl? She wants us to come here.
- No.
- Oh no, I had so many relationships.
- It's my first time meeting her.
I doubt it. You two might have come here
for a free meal before.
No. We will treat you for real today.
Normally, we won't do that.
- I doubt it.
- Our business has been well.
It's been great. Thank you for supporting us.
Our address is 1389 Huynh Tan Phat Street.
- District 7.
- Right.
This place is at A65. Kinda weird, right?
Alright, that's all.
One serving with no scallions.
- Alright.
- Extra scallions.
- Mine.
- One regular serving.
- Extra scallions, fewer noodles.
- And pure broth.
With an average amount of beef,
at the same price.
You can give me some.
Why is it crowded when it's newly opened?
- It is.
- The food is great.
- This place is great.
- There were famous eateries here in the past.
- Right.
- They were crowded in the evening.
- Most customers are bar goers.
- Right. They will come here to eat.
There are some bars opposite the market.
She knows it all.
She must be a player.
Well, I just happen to come here for a meal late at night.
- That is fast.
- So fast.
This is a special with fewer noodles.
So fast.
A five-way special with fewer noodles.
- This has scallions?
- Yes.
One bowl of scallions for me.
- And a bowl of chilies.
- Yes.
It's been a while... since I last met these two.
One bowl of... There it is.
You have to change your names.
Nga Mam and Hoang Anh Mam.
Both of you are.
So appealing.
The three servings are the same?
- Yes.
- They are.
- This one is better.
- It's plain.
- But I like it without scallions.
- This one.
- This one is good.
- Two teams here. One is with scallions and the other is not.
- Extra scallions for me.
- Yes.
It's satisfying to see a bowl without scallions.
- Yeah.
- We lack a pair of chopsticks.
I have mine.
A slice of lime, please.
Alright, try it.
Enjoy, everyone.
As always, I have to try the broth first.
Wait!
Nga, you just don't know how to eat it.
You have to try the original broth first.
Here.
- How is it?
- Let me try it.
We have to try the broth first before adding lime juice.
This must be bone broth. So savory.
It's fat free.
Because you added lime juice.
You won't know how it tastes.
Let's slow down.
I'm such a country bumpkin.
We will add culantro.
Here are the scallions.
Alright.
- Here are the scallion bulbs.
- Oh my!
Let's start seasoning.
Add more scallions.
I bet the beef balls are delicious too.
Gosh, the scallion bulbs look wonderful.
Oh, what's that?
Here's a special portion for Color Man.
I'm a big fan of yours.
OMG!
- Thanks to me, you've got a treat.
- I've watched The Lifetime Show,
- Street Cry and many more shows.
- I see.
This is a special part of the cow
- especially prepared for Color Man.
- Thank you.
May I know your name?
My name is Thong, Pham Minh Thong.
I see. Are you the owner?
I'm just the manager.
But I really adore you and the shows you produced.
You have watched all of them, huh?
- Of course. That's why I recognize you right away.
- How amazing! I was wearing a mask though.
What should I eat first?
Don't worry. Take your time.
The beef skirt is the most special part.
It's a rare ingredient.
Each cow only provides a few kgs of skirt.
- This is it?
- Yes. It's called 'beef skirt'.
- What's it called again?
- Beef skirt.
I see.
- You know about it?
- Nope.
All Nga cares about is eating.
Do you know what 'beef skirt' is?
- Am I saying it right?
- Yes. 'Beef skirt'.
Beef skirt is rare as each cow produces only a few kgs of it.
Which cut of the cow does it come from?
It's from the plate section.
- It's limited.
- The beef looks amazing.
Let me try it.
I will get back to this later.
- Enjoy, Color Man.
- Thank you, Mr. Thong.
Oh, beef skirt.
It looks great.
So friendly.
He gave me this.
Pho with beef balls.
If that is the name, it must be good.
- Yes.
- I think so.
- The beef balls are of high quality.
- This hoisin sauce looks appealing.
You have to make a dipping sauce.
Add satay and mix it all up.
Goodness, I would have had this
if I had knew he would give it to me.
With this bowl, I would be full until the evening.
This serving here is of the same size with
that in America.
- Remember? In America.
- I wasn't there.
Poor you.
- I visited Can Tho, Ca Mau, Soc Trang, Bac Lieu.
- It was My Tho.
Ah, I did visit My Tho.